{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '1466736038', 'answerTime': 'Mar 8, 2014', 'unixTime': 1394265600, 'question': 'Is there a SIM card in it?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': 'Yes. The Galaxy SIII accommodates a micro SIM card.'}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '1466736038', 'answerTime': 'Aug 4, 2014', 'unixTime': 1407135600, 'question': 'Why hasnt it upgraded to latest Android OS 4.4.2? Is it because it is unlocked? Some1 HELP ME!!!!!!', 'answer': "My S3 was able to upgrade to 4.4.2 last week, my service is with AT&T and it shouldn't matter if it locked or unlocked as my other phone is unlocked and was updated to 4.4.2 as well."}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '1466736038', 'answerTime': 'Jan 29, 2015', 'unixTime': 1422518400, 'question': 'Is this phone new, with 1 year manufacture warranty?', 'answerType': '?', 'answer': 'It is new but I was not able to get it activated with AT&T or Cricket so I had to return it.'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '1466736038', 'answerTime': 'Nov 30, 2014', 'unixTime': 1417334400, 'question': 'can in it be used abroad with a different carrier?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': 'Yes'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '1466736038', 'answerTime': 'Nov 24, 2014', 'unixTime': 1416816000, 'question': 'Is this phone brand new and NOT a mini?', 'answerType': '?', 'answer': 'The phone we received was exactly as described - a brand new Samsung SIII I747, AT&T branded but unlocked (and not a mini). It has worked perfectly on our AT&T service in USA for over a year (4G where available). I suggest you email the vendor and get a response email from them confirming the exact item you will receive.'}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '1466736038', 'answerTime': 'Nov 3, 2014', 'unixTime': 1415001600, 'question': 'What is the warranty on this?', 'answer': 'No warranty'}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '1466736038', 'answerTime': 'Oct 14, 2014', 'unixTime': 1413270000, 'question': 'this product is used with GSM chip in my country that is Venezuela?', 'answer': 'I am sure (but not positive) that this phone will work on the GSM network in Venezuela. However, this I747 model is primarily for the USA market where 4G is available. The I9300 is an international version of the Galaxy S3 that may be better for you and less expensive- just search for it on Amazon. Make sure to get an unlocked phone.'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '1466736038', 'answerTime': 'Oct 2, 2014', 'unixTime': 1412233200, 'question': 'Does this phone use the regular Sim card (the bigger Sim card)?', 'answerType': '?', 'answer': 'it takes mini sim'}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '1466736038', 'answerTime': 'Sep 11, 2014', 'unixTime': 1410418800, 'question': 'how much time you need to send me this product to miami?it could be before 21september of this year?', 'answer': 'If you choose expedited shipping you will have the phone in 2-3 days'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '1466736038', 'answerTime': 'Sep 3, 2014', 'unixTime': 1409727600, 'question': 'will this phone work with straight talk?', 'answerType': '?', 'answer': 'As an unlocked phone it is capable of working with any GSM Carrier providing their services using a SIM Card. However, we can only guarantee basic call and text, we recommend contacting your Carrier and making sure they provide their services to this model phone without any restrictions.'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '1621911888', 'answerTime': 'Dec 13, 2013', 'unixTime': 1386921600, 'question': 'Is it unlocked?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': 'yes'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '1621911888', 'answerTime': 'Dec 13, 2013', 'unixTime': 1386921600, 'question': 'Is it international?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': 'yes it is international.'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '1621911888', 'answerTime': 'Dec 8, 2013', 'unixTime': 1386489600, 'question': 'does this phone work with Verizon Wireless?', 'answerType': 'N', 'answer': 'No it will not work with verizon.'}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '1621911888', 'answerTime': 'Nov 27, 2013', 'unixTime': 1385539200, 'question': 'does it use regular sim or micro sim and does it has the micro sd slot. thanks', 'answer': 'Hi! This uses regular sim, and yes it does have micro sd slot.'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '1621911888', 'answerTime': 'Nov 3, 2013', 'unixTime': 1383462000, 'question': 'is it unlock?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': 'Yes'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '1621911888', 'answerTime': 'Sep 7, 2013', 'unixTime': 1378537200, 'question': 'Does the phone need SIM card to store contact list?', 'answerType': 'N', 'answer': 'No its not necessary. The phone have enough memory to store the contact list and more'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '1948701847', 'answerTime': 'Jan 3, 2014', 'unixTime': 1388736000, 'question': 'Does this allow me to charge my Iphone 4 to an iphone 5 connector?', 'answerType': '?', 'answer': 'No, this is for a micro USB cable. The Iphone 5 utilizes what is called a "lighting" connector.'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '1948701847', 'answerTime': 'Sep 26, 2014', 'unixTime': 1411714800, 'question': 'Will the use of this device allow me to use my iphone to play back my music over my car radio?', 'answerType': '?', 'answer': 'Well yeah it can.'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '1948701847', 'answerTime': 'Mar 27, 2014', 'unixTime': 1395903600, 'question': 'Will this allow me to play music on an iPhone 5 dock using an iPhone 4?', 'answerType': '?', 'answer': 'No.this is for Miscro can not used on iPhone 5.'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '1948701847', 'answerTime': 'Jan 24, 2015', 'unixTime': 1422086400, 'question': 'Will this allow me to play my 4th generation iPod on a docking station designed for 5th generation iPods?', 'answerType': '?', 'answer': "No! Don't buy it, I bought one and it didn't even fit! A waste of money"}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '1948701847', 'answerTime': 'May 4, 2014', 'unixTime': 1399186800, 'question': 'Can I use this to use an iphone 5 cable to convert to charge my ipad', 'answerType': '?', 'answer': 'Sadly as I learned the hard way no. It is for a droid type USB cable.'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '1948701847', 'answerTime': 'Oct 5, 2013', 'unixTime': 1380956400, 'question': 'will this convert a docking station used for charging an i4 so I can charge my new i5?', 'answerType': 'N', 'answer': 'This not good'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '3283005737', 'answerTime': 'Feb 22, 2014', 'unixTime': 1393056000, 'question': 'Does it come with all the current apps?', 'answerType': '?', 'answer': 'I have not added or deleted any apps since I received them. I know they browse the web over WiFi with ease. They come with all accessories and work perfectly and look brand new.'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '3283005737', 'answerTime': 'Feb 24, 2014', 'unixTime': 1393228800, 'question': 'Would they be activated to my personal Google account once I receive them?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': 'Yes, you can change them to whatever Gmail account you choose. Just note that it has to be a Gmail account. You would just have to factory reset them if you want to change to a different Gmail acct. Please let me know if you have any further questions and I would be happy to answer them. I also make google glass YouTube instructional Videos if you would like a link'}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '3283005737', 'answerTime': 'Feb 15, 2014', 'unixTime': 1392451200, 'question': 'who does this ship by? FED EX?', 'answer': 'Always. I never use any other carrier as FedEx has never given me a single problem about anything.'}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '3283005737', 'answerTime': 'May 26, 2014', 'unixTime': 1401087600, 'question': 'what is the diffrence with the Explorer Edition and the Explorer Edition (XE)2.0?', 'answer': '2.0 is the new one. More thin and simple'}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '3283005737', 'answerTime': 'Apr 3, 2015', 'unixTime': 1428044400, 'question': 'Real or frames, does it ship the actuall glasses or do you have to order them from Google after you order them from here?', 'answer': 'If you order mine it comes with everything. The Frame, the glass, and all accessories.'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '3283005737', 'answerTime': 'Nov 29, 2014', 'unixTime': 1417248000, 'question': 'Does in come in the original box ?', 'answerType': 'N', 'answer': 'No'}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '3283005737', 'answerTime': 'Nov 15, 2014', 'unixTime': 1416038400, 'question': 'Is the Explorer Edition the latest version out? I know there is a 1.0, 1.5 and 2.0 version, I am confused ~ is the Explorer the 2.0 version?', 'answer': 'Yes'}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '3283005737', 'answerTime': 'Sep 8, 2014', 'unixTime': 1410159600, 'question': 'Is it practical to read and listen to ebooks / audiobooks , or to watch a youtube video (10-30 min ) ?', 'answer': 'unable to watch youtube, read/listen to ebooks/audiobooks.....'}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '3283005737', 'answerTime': 'Jul 11, 2014', 'unixTime': 1405062000, 'question': 'What is different between normal and bundle?i have myopia ,so i wanna know where i can order the myopia glass ?', 'answer': 'Amazing&#65281;'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '3283005737', 'answerTime': 'Apr 19, 2014', 'unixTime': 1397890800, 'question': 'Is the Glass waterproof. Can I go diving with it?', 'answerType': '?', 'answer': 'It is not waterproof and would be ruined in submerged.'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '3998899561', 'answerTime': 'Nov 12, 2014', 'unixTime': 1415779200, 'question': 'Does this give any protection to the phone?', 'answerType': '?', 'answer': "It does wrap around the phone nicely. I didn't ever drop the phone with it on so I am not certain how that would work but I think it's decent."}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '3998899561', 'answerTime': 'May 9, 2014', 'unixTime': 1399618800, 'question': "I bought the Mophie yesterday. It's working fine so far. But this one has more mAh and much cheaper. Have any of you that own this had a Mophie?", 'answerType': '?', 'answer': "I've had my PowerBear for almost a month and a half. Where I work, I cannot always carry a charger so this can make my life great! The PowerBear works about half of the time I need to use it. Sometimes, when I turn it on, it won't provide the charge I need, but as soon as I connect it to my cord, for even a second and then unplug it, it suddenly becomes fully charged and able to work again as designed. When it does actually operate correctly, I can get an additional 30-70% battery life."}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '3998899561', 'answerTime': 'Apr 15, 2014', 'unixTime': 1397545200, 'question': 'Will this work for samsung galaxy s4 SGH-i337 (AT&amp;T)?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': "Yes if the charger portal is in the middle it'll be fine"}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '3998899561', 'answerTime': 'Mar 23, 2014', 'unixTime': 1395558000, 'question': 'Will this battery works with samsung galaxy s4 mini i9192?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': "Only if you find it for mini. The one I have it's just a regular Galaxy S4 from T-mobile. Lasts about another 50% extra on my battery."}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '3998899561', 'answerTime': 'Feb 20, 2014', 'unixTime': 1392883200, 'question': 'will this product work on the samsung galaxy s4 active?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': 'Yes it will.'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '3998899561', 'answerTime': 'Feb 3, 2014', 'unixTime': 1391414400, 'question': 'Will this work for a Samsung galaxy s4 active?', 'answerType': 'N', 'answer': 'No'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '3998899561', 'answerTime': 'Nov 12, 2014', 'unixTime': 1415779200, 'question': 'Does this give any protection to the phone?', 'answerType': '?', 'answer': "It does wrap around the phone nicely. I didn't ever drop the phone with it on so I am not certain how that would work but I think it's decent."}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '3998899561', 'answerTime': 'May 9, 2014', 'unixTime': 1399618800, 'question': "I bought the Mophie yesterday. It's working fine so far. But this one has more mAh and much cheaper. Have any of you that own this had a Mophie?", 'answerType': '?', 'answer': "I've had my PowerBear for almost a month and a half. Where I work, I cannot always carry a charger so this can make my life great! The PowerBear works about half of the time I need to use it. Sometimes, when I turn it on, it won't provide the charge I need, but as soon as I connect it to my cord, for even a second and then unplug it, it suddenly becomes fully charged and able to work again as designed. When it does actually operate correctly, I can get an additional 30-70% battery life."}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '3998899561', 'answerTime': 'Apr 15, 2014', 'unixTime': 1397545200, 'question': 'Will this work for samsung galaxy s4 SGH-i337 (AT&amp;T)?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': "Yes if the charger portal is in the middle it'll be fine"}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '3998899561', 'answerTime': 'Mar 23, 2014', 'unixTime': 1395558000, 'question': 'Will this battery works with samsung galaxy s4 mini i9192?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': "Only if you find it for mini. The one I have it's just a regular Galaxy S4 from T-mobile. Lasts about another 50% extra on my battery."}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '3998899561', 'answerTime': 'Feb 20, 2014', 'unixTime': 1392883200, 'question': 'will this product work on the samsung galaxy s4 active?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': 'Yes it will.'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '3998899561', 'answerTime': 'Feb 3, 2014', 'unixTime': 1391414400, 'question': 'Will this work for a Samsung galaxy s4 active?', 'answerType': 'N', 'answer': 'No'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '3998899561', 'answerTime': 'Nov 12, 2014', 'unixTime': 1415779200, 'question': 'Does this give any protection to the phone?', 'answerType': '?', 'answer': "It does wrap around the phone nicely. I didn't ever drop the phone with it on so I am not certain how that would work but I think it's decent."}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '3998899561', 'answerTime': 'May 9, 2014', 'unixTime': 1399618800, 'question': "I bought the Mophie yesterday. It's working fine so far. But this one has more mAh and much cheaper. Have any of you that own this had a Mophie?", 'answerType': '?', 'answer': "I've had my PowerBear for almost a month and a half. Where I work, I cannot always carry a charger so this can make my life great! The PowerBear works about half of the time I need to use it. Sometimes, when I turn it on, it won't provide the charge I need, but as soon as I connect it to my cord, for even a second and then unplug it, it suddenly becomes fully charged and able to work again as designed. When it does actually operate correctly, I can get an additional 30-70% battery life."}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '3998899561', 'answerTime': 'Apr 15, 2014', 'unixTime': 1397545200, 'question': 'Will this work for samsung galaxy s4 SGH-i337 (AT&amp;T)?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': "Yes if the charger portal is in the middle it'll be fine"}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '3998899561', 'answerTime': 'Mar 23, 2014', 'unixTime': 1395558000, 'question': 'Will this battery works with samsung galaxy s4 mini i9192?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': "Only if you find it for mini. The one I have it's just a regular Galaxy S4 from T-mobile. Lasts about another 50% extra on my battery."}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '3998899561', 'answerTime': 'Feb 20, 2014', 'unixTime': 1392883200, 'question': 'will this product work on the samsung galaxy s4 active?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': 'Yes it will.'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '3998899561', 'answerTime': 'Feb 3, 2014', 'unixTime': 1391414400, 'question': 'Will this work for a Samsung galaxy s4 active?', 'answerType': 'N', 'answer': 'No'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '6073894996', 'answerTime': 'May 10, 2014', 'unixTime': 1399705200, 'question': 'Is this an MINI car adapter', 'answerType': 'N', 'answer': "No it's regular car adapter size"}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '6073894996', 'answerTime': 'Mar 5, 2014', 'unixTime': 1394006400, 'question': 'will this charge samsung galaxy 4', 'answerType': '?', 'answer': 'This is a usb adapter. You need a usb samsung charger piece to connect it to your phone. plug usb port into your car&gt;&gt; plug your usb charger into the port&gt;&gt;then plug your phone to charge'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '6073894996', 'answerTime': 'Sep 28, 2014', 'unixTime': 1411887600, 'question': 'does it have a light', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': 'Yes'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '6073894996', 'answerTime': 'May 25, 2014', 'unixTime': 1401001200, 'question': 'will it charge iphone 5?', 'answerType': '?', 'answer': 'Most likely. I only have Motorola Droids.'}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '6073894996', 'answerTime': 'Jun 1, 2014', 'unixTime': 1401606000, 'question': 'How soon would I get it here in California?', 'answer': 'Dear: After you buy in my ship in 24 hours, cargo transportation in Hong Kong, need 7-21 working days. Thank you!'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '8288853439', 'answerTime': 'Jun 16, 2013', 'unixTime': 1371366000, 'question': 'does it work for Galaxy S 2', 'answerType': '?', 'answer': "yep, that's the phone I have"}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '8288853439', 'answerTime': 'Aug 22, 2013', 'unixTime': 1377154800, 'question': 'and for the Galaxy S4??', 'answer': 'This is compatible with all versions of the Samsung Galaxy, including the Galaxy S4'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '8288853439', 'answerTime': 'May 6, 2014', 'unixTime': 1399359600, 'question': 'Does it work on the T-Mobile Samsung Galaxy S1 (USA Version)?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': 'Yes it does,matter of fact I have the reflex works perfectly'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '8288853439', 'answerTime': 'Mar 28, 2014', 'unixTime': 1395990000, 'question': 'does it work for htc one?', 'answerType': '?', 'answer': "We're using this to charge a Galaxy S3 &Note 2. Should work the HTC One."}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '8288853439', 'answerTime': 'Dec 25, 2013', 'unixTime': 1387958400, 'question': 'Does this work on both 110 Volt (USA) and 220 Volt (Europe)?', 'answerType': '?', 'answer': "Hi Sam, that's a great question, but unfortunately I don't have a complete answer for you. I can only say yes to USA.. sorry I can't help you for Europe.."}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '8288853439', 'answerTime': 'Dec 2, 2013', 'unixTime': 1385971200, 'question': 'Is it 1 amp or 2 amp output?', 'answer': 'One amp'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '8288853439', 'answerTime': 'Nov 28, 2013', 'unixTime': 1385625600, 'question': 'does it work for nexus 7 tablet', 'answerType': '?', 'answer': "I'm afraid that this was used for the Samsung galaxy 3s. It works fine with the galaxy although it seems its not charging as quickly after 1 week usage. I really couldn't say if it works with the nexus 7 tablet. Sorry:("}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '8288853439', 'answerTime': 'Oct 29, 2013', 'unixTime': 1383030000, 'question': 'How long does a full charge take?', 'answer': 'Maybe an hour guesstimate.'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '8288853439', 'answerTime': 'Oct 9, 2013', 'unixTime': 1381302000, 'question': 'Does it work for galaxy s3?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': 'Yes it does. They have the same charging port.'}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '8288853439', 'answerTime': 'Jul 30, 2013', 'unixTime': 1375167600, 'question': 'How long is the cord?', 'answer': 'The cord is 60 inches long and pretty durable'}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '8288878881', 'answerTime': 'Oct 29, 2013', 'unixTime': 1383030000, 'question': 'How long is the cord?', 'answer': 'About 4 ft'}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '8288878881', 'answerTime': 'Mar 28, 2014', 'unixTime': 1395990000, 'question': 'What is the output in AMPS? (Example 500mA or 1A or 2A)', 'answer': '1A. I had to get a magnifying glass to read it. Very tiny print.'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '8288878881', 'answerTime': 'Aug 23, 2014', 'unixTime': 1408777200, 'question': "Does it power the Samsung Galaxy S II SGH-1777? I've purchased 2 car chargers that claim to charge this model and haven't. Thank you.", 'answerType': '?', 'answer': 'It does. Problem with mine was the spot to plug in charger is broken. I use an external charger'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '8288878881', 'answerTime': 'Dec 10, 2014', 'unixTime': 1418198400, 'question': 'Does the computer recognize the phone while using this cable? I want to be able to transfer files, and upgrade my phone using a computer.', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': "Yes, I'm more than certain it does. :-)"}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '8288878881', 'answerTime': 'Jun 6, 2014', 'unixTime': 1402038000, 'question': 'does it take a long time to fully charge your phone?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': 'Yes. My phone started acting really weird so I discontinued using that particular charger.'}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '8288878881', 'answerTime': 'Mar 15, 2014', 'unixTime': 1394866800, 'question': "I'm assuming this charger would work with a Galaxy Discover? Looks like it should,,,,,,", 'answer': "I'm no expert on Samsung products, but I believe that the charge port on their devices are consistant. Hope this helps"}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '8288878881', 'answerTime': 'Feb 22, 2014', 'unixTime': 1393056000, 'question': 'This says S2, does anyone know if it works on a SIII Galaxy?', 'answer': "That I don't know sorry, I know it works for the Galaxy S and the S2 but not sure about the S3 sorry"}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '8288878881', 'answerTime': 'Jan 27, 2014', 'unixTime': 1390809600, 'question': 'can I use it in Europe with a converter to 220V ?', 'answerType': '?', 'answer': "I'm sorry. I don't know if you can do that."}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '8288878881', 'answerTime': 'Jan 25, 2014', 'unixTime': 1390636800, 'question': 'Is this compatitble with Samsung Galaxy S II LTE I9210?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': 'Yes it is compatible with Samsung galaxy s2'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '8288878881', 'answerTime': 'Dec 12, 2013', 'unixTime': 1386835200, 'question': 'Will it work with my samsung convoy?', 'answerType': '?', 'answer': "Not sure if it will of not. But the supplier told me, this was an older version and you can't use your phone or access the screen while charging. I hope this helps."}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '9864799924', 'answerTime': 'Mar 12, 2015', 'unixTime': 1426143600, 'question': 'Does this support my LG G Pad 10.1 V700?', 'answerType': '?', 'answer': 'I honestly am not sure. It should as I just plugged my g pad 8.3 (through Verizon) in and it instantly connected. Honestly when I looked for a slim port adapter I never looked at compatability. Best of luck!'}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '9864799924', 'answerTime': 'Mar 5, 2015', 'unixTime': 1425542400, 'question': "Will this work with an LG G3 and an LG G Pad? showing the LG's display on your TV?", 'answer': 'this is the only micro usb to hdmi cable that is compatible with the LG G3'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '9864799924', 'answerTime': 'Mar 5, 2015', 'unixTime': 1425542400, 'question': 'Will this work with my LG Gpad 8.3 LTE tablet or my LG G3 phone?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': 'Works with LG G3. And probably any other item with the same type of micro port. I have used it with all of my various devices.'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '9864799924', 'answerTime': 'Feb 2, 2015', 'unixTime': 1422864000, 'question': 'Does this product work with Nexus 7 2012 model?', 'answerType': 'N', 'answer': 'No, The first gen Nexus 7 Tablet does not support micro HDMI out. I believe the second gen does though.'}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '9864799924', 'answerTime': 'Jan 6, 2015', 'unixTime': 1420531200, 'question': "Wil this work with a Samsung Galaxy s5? I've been trying to find a good connector for GS5 to 4k TV?", 'answer': 'Not 100% percent sure about the s5, but it does not work with the s4. That one takes an MHL adaptor.'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '9864799924', 'answerTime': 'Nov 19, 2014', 'unixTime': 1416384000, 'question': 'Will this work with a 10" Toshiba thrive ICS tablet? The thrive has a mini usb port.', 'answerType': 'N', 'answer': 'No'}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '9864799924', 'answerTime': 'Aug 8, 2014', 'unixTime': 1407481200, 'question': 'i have the lg g3 and it requires 3.0 or higher will this device work?', 'answer': "I have the LG g2 and it works very poorly on that and my friends LG g3 doesn't work at all with it it may just be my unit but I highly recommend something else"}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '9864799924', 'answerTime': 'Jun 27, 2014', 'unixTime': 1403852400, 'question': 'Will the work with lg optimus g ls970?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': 'It works with my Google Nexus 5 phone, which is manufactured by LG so my best GUESS is that it would work with your LG phone. But to be sure check with LG.'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '9864799924', 'answerTime': 'May 18, 2014', 'unixTime': 1400396400, 'question': 'Will this work with chromebook 11', 'answerType': 'N', 'answer': 'Sorry.... Not sure....'}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '9864799924', 'answerTime': 'Feb 12, 2014', 'unixTime': 1392192000, 'question': "It's compatible for Dell Venue 8 Android Tablet , work on this Tablet Dell Venue 8 Android ?", 'answer': 'Currently, Dell says no support via Micro-USB via MHL or SlimPort. But it'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '9966685472', 'answerTime': 'Dec 7, 2014', 'unixTime': 1417939200, 'question': 'Does this work with a Samsung NOTE 4?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': 'Yes it does'}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '9966685472', 'answerTime': 'Jul 5, 2013', 'unixTime': 1373007600, 'question': 'I experienced all that you said with the Samsung Adapter. The Samsung in Texas said it is "GUARANTEED ONLY ON SAMSUNG TV\'s, cables &amp; power adapters?', 'answer': "I am not sure how to answer that because I am not sure if you even really asked a question. You have a question mark at the end, but it seems like more of a statement or an assertion. Are you asking me or telling me? And even if you are asking me a question about what Samsung told you, I don't know what I can tell you regarding a conversation I was not a part of. Here is what I can tell you. I have another MHL adapter purchased from a different vendor and it works perfectly on all of my HD televisions, and none of those televisions are made by Samsung. So it should work on any television regardless of the manufacturer. This is for wired mirroring with the MHL adapter. There is also wireless mirroring. This is different. Wireless mirroring is what requires a change to the settings in your phone. I know that this type of mirroring, at this point in time, does only work with Samsung brand televisions or with the use of a peripheral Samsung brand dongle. So perhaps the person you spoke with was just confused as to what you were actually trying to do and gave you advice about wireless mirroring instead of wired. As for the cables needing to be made by Samsung, that is just a joke. No matter what the brand is, all HDMI cables of the same rating are built the same. There is no proprietary technology in them. They are just an inert conduit to transfer a signal. The biggest difference between HDMI cables is what they use for shielding, and that just impacts signal clarity and will not cause incompatibility. As for the power adapter, there are plenty of technical tutorials that say you do not have to have a Samsung brand power supply. I believe Samsung's own literature that came with the MHL adapter also stated that third-party power supplies can be used. Now the power supply does have to be of a specific power rating. Samsung GS4 power supplies are the correct power rating. (As one would expect.) But I believe the manual itself says you can use other power supplies. (It is hard to remember since I read from so many sources.) So at least some of what that representative told you just seems silly and does not make sense. And that does not give me much confidence in the rest of what they told you. Whenever I get strange answers I just call back, get a different person, and ask again. Don't be surprised if you get a different answer. At the very least though, if your MHL adapter does not work then just return it to whoever you bought it from and avoid dealing with Samsung all together."}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '9966685472', 'answerTime': '19 days ago', 'question': 'Does this work with Note 4 and Sony tv?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': 'I only used it with my s4 phone it will work on any TV with HDMI conn! I used it with my old L G . I have an UDHTV SAMSUN now. Harry J'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '9966685472', 'answerTime': 'Mar 16, 2015', 'unixTime': 1426489200, 'question': 'Does this work with Samsung note 2?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': "Yes. That's what I have. U will also need HDMI cable with it. This is just the adaptor."}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '9966685472', 'answerTime': 'Feb 1, 2015', 'unixTime': 1422777600, 'question': 'I reviewed this product and it does work with TAB S 10.5 OLMED display, however, It will not charge as your using it. But it will display.', 'answer': 'Is there a question here?'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '9966685472', 'answerTime': 'Jan 28, 2015', 'unixTime': 1422432000, 'question': 'Does this work with Galaxy Tab 4?', 'answerType': '?', 'answer': "It didn't work for my galaxy tab 4 2014. Not even for tab3. T211. I don't know if mine is defective or not compatible. Good luck."}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '9966685472', 'answerTime': 'Dec 28, 2014', 'unixTime': 1419753600, 'question': 'Has anyone gotten this cable to work with the Galaxy S4? If so, which seller did you purchase your cable from?', 'answer': "Yes this adapter works great with the galaxy s4. be mindful, I have experienced in hotel rooms most of the wall outlets don't have enough power to use the MHL adapter and charge the battery. (if you don't have an extended battery you probably won't make it through much more than a movie on a full charge) Most other outlets have worked just fine. I am not sure which seller I purchased from. I hope this helps!! :)"}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '9966685472', 'answerTime': 'Dec 16, 2014', 'unixTime': 1418716800, 'question': 'Does this work with a Samsung Galaxy TabS model SM-T800?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': 'Probably yes it will. I have a Samsung Galaxy Tab 3 and it works fine.'}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '9966685472', 'answerTime': 'Oct 13, 2014', 'unixTime': 1413183600, 'question': 'This device works with the Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.0 in March?', 'answer': "Yes it does a little buggy,you'll come out better with a chromecast now"}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '9966685472', 'answerTime': 'Sep 2, 2014', 'unixTime': 1409641200, 'question': 'This device operates in the samsung galaxy SGH i717???', 'answer': "This device doesn't work for any samsung galaxy. I have SCH-1545 never work, waste of many for something shouldn't be in the market"}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '9985558634', 'answerTime': 'Nov 29, 2013', 'unixTime': 1385712000, 'question': 'Will this fit the Coby MP757-8G player?', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': 'yes !! this does fit the player i bought it when i got my.'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '9985558634', 'answerTime': 'Sep 22, 2014', 'unixTime': 1411369200, 'question': 'Will this fit the COBY MP707-4G player?', 'answerType': '?', 'answer': 'They say that this will fit COBY MP3 Players, but it does not. Coby MP3 players use a Mini-USB Plug. My advise is to contact COBY directy and have them send you one. Hope this helps.'}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '9985558634', 'answerTime': 'Nov 30, 2013', 'unixTime': 1385798400, 'question': "Where can I go to put some videos on this player? I'm not familiar with the format described in the instructions booklet. Thanks.", 'answer': 'I don\'t know, this was a horrible choice of purchase. I bought it and it broke within the first couple of days. The formatting is off and the instructions manual is worse. The number to contact tech support (which was located inside the packet) is hoax, it\'s invalid and keeps saying the "leave a message" therefore, you will not be able to speak with anyone about the product. It was so cheap and would never recommend anyone buying it. It was a waste of money and would never buy coby again.'}
{'questionType': 'open-ended', 'asin': '9985558634', 'answerTime': 'Nov 30, 2013', 'unixTime': 1385798400, 'question': 'It will work on a 220 electric outlet? In sudamerica ?', 'answer': 'I doubt it. The outlet should be configured differently, similar to a 220 here in the states. I would also be wary of putting so much juice to a device like this. Nice little player, however. I use mine a lot. Hope this helps.'}
{'questionType': 'yes/no', 'asin': '9985558634', 'answerTime': 'Jul 19, 2013', 'unixTime': 1374217200, 'question': 'My Coby620 4 GB MP3 player has a rechargable lithium-polymer battery; will this charger work with it', 'answerType': 'Y', 'answer': 'I do believe if it fits it will work!'}